Joel Jang

Last updated on Feb 18, 2023

joeljang.github.io ◆ joeljang@kaist.ac.kr

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My main research goal is to build large neural models that are applicable to real-world scenarios, by addressing inherent limitations of current neural models. Specifically, I am interested in allowing neural models to be lifelong learners [C1, C2, P1], providing privacy and security guarantees for neural models [P2], and enabling neural models to follow the given instruction via prompt [W1, C3, P3, P4].

EDUCATION

M.S. in Artificial Intelligence

Seoul, Korea

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

03/2021 - 08/2023

Graduate School of AI | Language & Knowledge Lab

Advisor: Minjoon Seo

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering

Seoul, Korea

03/2017 - 02/2021

Korea University

PUBLICATIONS

Conference Papers

[C3] Guess the Instruction! Making Language Models Stronger Zero-shot Learners Seonghyeon Ye, Doyoung Kim, **Joel Jang**, Joongbo Shin, Minjoon Seo ICLR 2023 [paper][code]

[C2] TemporalWiki: A Lifelong Benchmark for Training and Evaluating Ever-Evolving Language Models **Joel Jang***, Seonghyeon Ye*, Changho Lee, Sohee Yang, Joongbo Shin, Janghoon Han, Gyeonghun Kim, Minjoon Seo

EMNLP 2022 [paper][code]

[C1] Towards Continual Knowledge Learning of Language Models **Joel Jang**, Seonghyeon Ye, Sohee Yang, Joongbo Shin, Janghoon Han, Gyeonghun Kim, Stanley Jungkyu Choi, Minjoon Seo ICLR 2022 [paper] [code]

Workshop Papers

[W1] Can Large Language Models Truly Follow Your Instructions? Case-study with Negated Prompts **Joel Jang***, Seonghyeon Ye*, Minjoon Seo NeurIPS 2022 Workshop on Transfer Learning for NLP (TL4NLP) [paper][code]

Journal Papers

[J2] Sequential Targeting: A Continual Learning Approach for Data Imbalance in Text Classification **Joel Jang**, Yoonjeon Kim, Kyoungho Choi, Sungho Suh Expert Systems With Applications (2021) [paper] [code]

[J1] Supervised Health Stage Prediction Using Convolution Neural Networks for Bearing Wear Sungho Suh, **Joel Jang**, Seungjae Won, Mayank S. Jha, Yong Oh Lee Sensors (2020) [paper] [code]

Preprints

[P4] Gradient Ascent Post-training Enhances Language Model Generalization Dongkeun Yoon*, **Joel Jang***, Sungdong Kim, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ACL 2023*

[P3] Retrieval of Soft Prompt Enhances Zero-shot Task Generalization Seonghyeon Ye, **Joel Jang**, Doyoung Kim, Yongrae Jo, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ACL 2023* [paper][code]

[P2] Knowledge Unlearning for Mitigating Privacy Risks in Language Models **Joel Jang**, Dongkeun Yoon, Sohee Yang, Sungmin Cha, Moontae Lee, Lajanugen Logeswaran, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ACL 2023* [paper][code]

[P1] Fixed Input Parameterization for Efficient Prompting Eunbi Choi, Yongrae Jo, **Joel Jang**, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ACL 2023*, [paper][code]

EXPERIENCE

Allen Institute of AI (AI2) | Mosaic Team

Seattle, US

Research Intern 06/2023-

To Be Decided

LG AI Research Seoul, Korea

Research Intern (Host: Moontae Lee, Lajanugen Logeswaran)

07/2022-Current

Working on (1) knowledge unlearning for LMs & (2) unseen task generalization with expert LMs

Kakao Brain Seongnam, Korea

Research Intern (Host: Ildoo Kim)

12/2020-02/2021

Worked on large-scale representation learning with weak supervision of images and caption data using TPUs

NAVER Seongnam, Korea

Software Engineer Intern

07/2020-09/2020

Worked on hate speech detection model, AI Clean Bot 2.0 (40+ million monthly users, >80% of Korean population) Developed novel method of handling data imbalance using continual learning (*paper published under ESWA*)

KIST Europe Saarbrucken, Germany

Research Intern (Host: Yong Oh Lee)

08/2019-01/2020

Worked on anomaly detection & remaining useful life prediction of machinery (*paper published under Sensors*) Gave an Oral Presentation at *PHM Korea 2020* (2020. 07. 23)

SERVICES

Conference Reviewer

COLING 2022, EMNLP 2022, AKBC 2022, ICLR 2023, ACL 2023

Journal Reviewer

Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research (JAIR)

MENTORING

06/2022-Current	Dongkeun Yoon, B.S. Student, Dongguk University
06/2022-Current	Seungone Kim , B.S. Student, Yonsei → M.S. Student, KAIST
10/2021-05/2022	Changho Lee, B.S. Student, Korea University → LG AI Research
06/2021-02/2022	Seonghyeon Ye , B.S. Student, KAIST → M.S./Ph.D. Student, KAIST

TEACHING

(KAIST AI599) AI for Law		09/2022-12/2022
Teaching Assistant (TA)		
(KAIST AI605) Deep Learning for	NLP	03/2022-06/2022
Teaching Assistant (TA)		

I

INVITED TALKS	
Expert Language Models UNC at Chapel Hill (Host: Colin Raffel)	02/2023
Temporal Adaptation of Language Models Korean AI Association Summer NLP Session (Host: Minjoon Seo)	08/2022
Temporal Adaptation of Language Models KAIST School of Computing (Host: Alice Oh)	07/2022
Temporal Adaptation of Language Models	05/2022

HONORS AND AWARDS

Hyperconnect (Host: Buru Chang)

Qualcomm Innovation Fellowship Korea (QIFK) 2022 Grand Prize in Graduation Capstone Competition (Best Paper Award), 2020 (Advisor: Jaewoo Kang) 4th place, AI NLP Challenge Enliple Cup, 2020 3rd place, HAAFOR Challenge 2019 Future Global Leader Scholarships, Korea University, 2019

Best Innovation Award, Intel AI Drone Hackathon, 2018

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Bilingual in English (2004-2016 in US) and Korean (native)

GRE: 326 (Verbal, 157/170, 76th Percentile) | Quant, 169/170, 95th Percentile | Writing, 5.0/6.0, 92nd Percentile)

TOEFL: 119/120 (Reading, 30 | Listening, 30 | Speaking, 29 | Writing, 30)

SAT: 1530/1600 (Reading and Writing, 730 | Math, 800)

Conversational in Chinese